♪I want to get closer♪
♪ اريد الاقتراب ♪
♪I walk lightly♪
♪ أمشي بخفة ♪
♪Yet accidentally♪
♪ لكن بالصدفة ♪
♪Walk into your trap of love♪
♪ ادخل في فخ الحب
♪Oh no, no, no♪
♪ أوه لا ، لا ، لا
♪You cannot simply confess your love when you are drunk♪
لا يمكنك ببساطة الاعتراف بحبك وأنت في حالة سكر ♪
=Campus Ace=
= الحرم الجامعي آيس =
=Episode 19= (101 methods to confess)
= الحلقة 19 = (101 طريقة للاعتراف)
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
No way.
مستحيل.
Be my girlfriend.
كوني حبيبتي.
Impossible.
غير ممكن.
I can't do it.
لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
I really can't.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع.
Confession is an essential step
الاعتراف خطوة أساسية
to begin a new relationship.
لبدء علاقة جديدة.
No.
رقم.
You need to do it.
تحتاج إلى القيام بذلك.
Hey!
يا!
What are you drawing?
ماذا ترسم؟
We aren't in that kind of relationship.
نحن لسنا في هذا النوع من العلاقات.
I have plenty of proof
لدي الكثير من الأدلة
that you're dating.
بأنك تواعد.
But even if I like him,
لكن حتى لو أحبه ،
he may not feel the same way about me.
قد لا يشعر بنفس الشعور تجاهي.
Must I tell her that I like her?
هل يجب أن أخبرها أنني معجب بها؟
Action is what matters.
العمل هو ما يهم.
What if I misunderstood
ماذا لو أسأت الفهم
his feelings for me?
مشاعره بالنسبة لي؟
I've been good to her all this while.
لقد كنت جيدًا معها طوال هذا الوقت.
She should've felt it already.
كان يجب أن تشعر به بالفعل.
For girls,
للفتيات،
clarifying your feelings
توضيح مشاعرك
is a sign of responsibility.
هي علامة على المسؤولية.
It even gives her a sense of security.
بل إنه يمنحها إحساسًا بالأمان.
It is also to show
هو أيضا لإظهار
that your relationship
أن علاقتك
is meaningful.
ذات مغزى.
You're awesome as always.
أنت رائع كالعادة.
You know a lot.
انت تعرف الكثير.
I surely do.
أنا بالتأكيد أفعل.
Action is the most direct.
العمل هو الأكثر مباشرة.
Confession
اعتراف
doesn't really suit me.
لا يناسبني حقًا.
Life still needs a sense of occasion.
لا تزال الحياة بحاجة إلى إحساس بالمناسبة.
But how should I confess?
لكن كيف أعترف؟
I have no choice but to use my ultimate skill.
ليس لدي خيار سوى استخدام مهارتي المطلقة.
Read this.
اقرا هذا.
101 methods to confess.
101 طريقة للاعتراف.
Will it really work?
هل ستنجح حقا؟
They'll come in to play basketball from that way.
سوف يأتون للعب كرة السلة بهذه الطريقة.
Then
ثم
it's your best time to confess.
إنه أفضل وقت لك للاعتراف.
No.
رقم.
I think I'm not ready.
أعتقد أنني لست مستعدًا.
You're the bravest female warrior.
أنت أشجع محاربة.
Go for it.
أذهب خلفها.
Xiao'ai.
شياو.
Let's forget it.
دعونا ننسى ذلك.
Sit down.
اجلس.
I think this method doesn't suit me.
أعتقد أن هذه الطريقة لا تناسبني.
You're only one step away.
أنت على بعد خطوة واحدة فقط.
Don't be a coward.
لا تكن جبانا.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
It's very simple.
انها بسيطة جدا.
I'll teach you.
سوف اعلمك.
Just do this.
فقط افعل هذا.
(I have something very important to tell you.)
(لدي شيء مهم جدًا أخبرك به.)
(This matters to me,)
(هذا يهمني ،)
(but you matter the most to me!)
(لكنك تهمني أكثر!)
(It was a pleasure to meet you)
(كان لقائك من دواعي سروري)
(and we have so much fun together.)
(ولدينا الكثير من المرح معًا.)
(I like you. Will you be my boyfriend?)
(أنا معجب بك. هل ستكون صديقي؟)
Well,
نحن سوف،
what do you think of this kind of confession?
ما رأيك في هذا النوع من الاعتراف؟
I will!
أنا سوف!
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
You may have misunderstood it.
ربما تكون قد أسأت فهمه.
We're just...
كانوا مجرد...
It's not what you think.
ليست كما تعتقد.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Xiao'ai.
شياو.
I accept your confession to me.
أنا أقبل اعترافك لي.
You're responsible for me.
أنت مسؤول عني.
No.
رقم.
Be responsible.
كن مسؤولا.
Later,
في وقت لاحق،
just do as I've told you.
فقط افعل كما أخبرتك.
Then,
ثم،
it will work out.
سوف تنجح.
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
That's a sure thing.
هذا أمر مؤكد.
She is coming.
هي قادمة.
You're all by yourself.
أنت وحدك.
Good luck.
حظا طيبا وفقك الله.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Mother.
الأم.
Feifei said you haven't contacted her for a month.
قالت فايفي إنك لم تتصل بها منذ شهر.
You're fiddling around here.
أنت تتلاعب هنا.
I'm venturing.
أنا أغامر.
In both romance and career.
في كل من الرومانسية والوظيفة.
I'm not fiddling around.
أنا لا أعبث.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You must be Yao's older sister.
يجب أن تكون أخت ياو الكبرى.
I'm his partner.
أنا شريكه.
Well,
نحن سوف،
this is our newly ventured application.
هذا هو تطبيقنا الجديد.
Look.
نظرة.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
this method of confession
طريقة الاعتراف هذه
is too old-fashioned.
قديم جدا.
Ling Yao.
لينغ ياو.
Momo.
مومو.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I...
أنا...
I like you, too.
أنامعجب بك أيضا.
♪Hey, do not blink at me♪
♪ مهلا ، لا ترمش في وجهي
♪I don't want to talk about love all day♪
♪ لا أريد التحدث عن الحب طوال اليوم
♪Hey, remember to reply to me♪
♪ مهلا ، تذكر الرد علي ♪
♪You always sigh and say I am stupid♪
♪ أنت دائمًا تتنهد وتقول إنني غبي ♪
♪For not knowing how you think♪
لعدم معرفتك كيف تفكر ♪
♪I want to get closer♪
♪ اريد الاقتراب ♪
♪I walk lightly♪
♪ أمشي بخفة ♪
♪Yet accidentally♪
♪ لكن بالصدفة ♪
♪Walk into your trap of love♪
♪ ادخل في فخ الحب
♪You love bumping into her♪
♪ أنت تحب الاصطدام بها
♪On every sunny day♪
♪ في كل يوم مشمس
♪Approach gently♪
♪ اقترب برفق ♪
♪My letter of love confession♪
♪ رسالتي اعتراف بالحب ♪
♪I chat shyly with her♪
♪ أتحدث معها بخجل ♪
♪While avoiding her gaze♪
مع تجنب نظرتها ♪
♪I predict our destiny♪
♪ أتوقع مصيرنا ♪
♪We are not lovers yet♪
♪ لسنا عشاق بعد ♪